It's inappropriate to use remove operaiton and next operation together. It's a unsafe operaton. Same case as back operation and remove operation.
We support unsafe operation to remove a element in an iterative process.
We divide insert operation into two operations, which one of them has already been encapsulated in node constructor and another not.
We could set one node's previous node and next node by using node constructor, but we need redirect relationship for orignal node and its previous node or next node.
